Fire.
Close, far.
The same, different.
This is a stomach.
There are subtitles if you need them, don't forget to turn them on.
This is a random calendar, and this is an advent calendar.
It has chocolate ... inside.
Outside, inside.
And each window has a number.
I have left the chocolates of the 23 and 24 to eat them with you.
This is a shooting star and even if it's cheap chocolate, I love it.
At the bottom, the closest to us:
Close, far, close, far.
What we have closer, are The Three Wise Men, mounted on their camels.
The camel is this animal and the camel has two humps.
Humans don't ... we don't want humps. We can have humps but we don't want humps.
Because they hurts.
And the camels, in those humps they have ...
Do you know? If you know what camels have on their humps, leave it in a comment.
So here are the Three Wise Men and their names are Melchor Gaspar and Baltasar.
Mind you, I don't know who is who.
But each one brings a gift.
See? Here in their hands they have something and this is a gift.
And each gift is different.
It is not the same, the same.
They are different, different.
The Wise Men bring gold, incense and myrrh.
On the right we have a stone well and above the well:
Above, below.
There is a cat, an orange cat.
Maybe it's Garfield.
An orange cat and the bowl of water for the cat, so that it does not get thirsty.
I'm thirsty, I want water.
When you are thirsty, you drink water.
Next to the well there is a smiling lady:
She is not angry and she is not sad. She's happy, she's smiling.
And in her arms she is holding holding a basket full of bread.
Right in front of the well, over window number 16,
there are two little mice and one of them is holding in its little hands,
or well, mice don't have hands.
In its clutches. It's claws. Wolverine. Claws.
He's holding, he's holding a piece of cheese.
What is that? That is cheese.
Behind the lady there's a house, a yellow brick house.
Down there it looks like there are two entrances:
Here is an entrance with a door and here is an entrance without a door.
Without, it has no door.
And on the top floor, the second floor there is another girl
smiling and waving, greeting the Three Wise Men who are coming in her direction.
In the direction of the girl.
Next to the house, there is a boy with curly hair
and he is holding some wooden sticks ...
I don't know if you can see it, this stick is transparent. You can see through the stick.
It is a special stick. Special is a very easy word.
It's like in English special, but with an E at the beginning: e + special.
Well, these sticks seem to be firewood, firewood to start a fire.
Fire.
I just wasted a match. This is a match.
This way, if we follow the path.
See? Here is a path, a little path.
In the middle of the road, in the middle like Thursday.
That's an expression: you're in the middle like Thursday Ramón, get out!
In the middle of the road, there is a man who looks like, looks like, looks like a shepherd.
Because the cane is made out of wood, like the firewood.
Not a candy cane,
and a few sheep, there are two sheep.
And this sheep is eating grass.
Where does that grass come from?
I don't know, because here I only see dirt,
I don't see grass, I don't see grass. I don't know where the sheep got it from.
To the man's left, to our left because for him it would be on his right.
To our left there is another little house but this house only has one floor.
This is not a floor plan but a floor plan.
My building has 13 floors, -which are not these- and this house only has one floor.
A boy looks out the window, looks out.
And he is like this, in this position.
A boy who is also watching the Magi arrive.
Behind the house, there is an orange cow.
Why is the cow orange?
Good question, I would like to ask the illustrator, but he does not say who he is.
A shame
The cow is also eating, it is chewing grass.
By the way, how many stomachs do cows have?
What is a stomach?
This is a stomach.
Winnie-The-Pooh's stomach is full of honey, my stomach is full of chocolate.
Next to the cow there is a goat and well we have two goats:
a goat here and a goat here, two.
One is white and the other is a little yellowish, maybe it's older.
Or maybe it's dirtier, we don't know.
This goat belongs to this boy and this boy has a tambourine in his hand.
This is my tambourine, to sing Christmas carols. You see Here it says my name: Laura.
Here on the other side, on the other side of the road, there is a hen and her chicks and a rooster.
The one who bothers you in the morning by doing:
The rooster cackles in the morning.
Arriving at the cave this is a stone cave I imagine.
Inside the cave there happens to be a lantern.
They have been very lucky that they have found a cave
with a lantern that has a candle inside to give light.
To give light and illumination, not to give birth.
Giving birth is what Maria is going to do in this cave.
She is going to give birth to Jesus and Jesus is going to enter this world.
In this photo Jesus has already been born and here next to us we have José, who has a very thick beard.
It means that it has a lot of hair and is very thick.
A city can also be very populated.
And next to it is an ox and a donkey.
This is Maria who is very happy, it does not seem at all that she has just given birth.
Above the cave there is an angel, a little angel.
It has its wings, with feathers like the rooster and the hen,
and here are two very cute bunnies: one white and one brown.
And above, the white bunny is looking at a shooting star:
A shooting star of these that do:
And here is a single tree and this tree is a palm tree.
You have normal palm trees, and coconut trees that give you coconuts.
I'm going to do an unboxing.
And nothing subscribe and so you can learn more Spanish with me, learn in a fun way-
I just got a cut that c *** in the l ****.
For being stupid.
Subscribe you go, I have cut myself.
Let's finish unboxing this one at least.
For my balls I finish it.
Ahhh Milk. It is stuck.
Omg. I just cut myself again.